Guide to the H.E Butti Bin Bishr Collection AD.MC.093
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Members of the UAE Delegation's Visit to Pakistan
  - A portrait of H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan arriving to a country., Circa 1969-1971; AD_MC_093_ref19_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x 30.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Presidents; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Men; Individual Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Royalty
  - A group of members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegation at a formal dinner for the arrival of the Emirati delegation, including H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (second from the right), Ayub Khan (fifth from the right), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr sitting with H.E. H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim in the back., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Presidents; Men; Group Portraits; Pakistan; Head Covers/Veils; Waiting staff/Servers; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Bow Ties; Microphones; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Hats; Flower Garlands/Bouquets
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (on right of couch) talking with a member of the Pakistani delegation and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (back facing viewer)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x 30.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Mirrors; Pakistan
  - A group of four men sitting on armchairs including H.E. Abdullah Al Dhahi (foreground), and H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi (in military uniform) next to. H.E. Butti Bin Bishr during the Emirati delegation's visit to Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x 31 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Pakistan; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Cigarettes; Officials
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (front middle) with H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (front left) leading members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegation upon arrival to Pakistan. Below the leftmost lamp post includes (from the left): H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, Ahmab Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.4 x 30.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Street Lamps; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Officials; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Crowds; Gatherings; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Mountains/Hills; Buildings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) with an unidentified man during a trip overseas., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 30.4 x 25.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Unknown Locations; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair; Hats; Cats; Transportation
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nayhan (left) with an unidentified man during a trip overseas., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref19_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records AD_MC_093)
  - Members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegation in discussion upon the the arrival of the Emirati delegation, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right), H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim (fourth from the left), and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (third from the left)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 23.8 x 29.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Pakistan; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Furnishings; Cigarettes; Carpets/Rugs; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Clocks/Watches; Paintings; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages
  - From the left: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef having tea during the UAE visit to Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Furnishings; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left) with H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (middle) looking at images., Circa 1968-1969; AD_MC_093_ref19_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Unknown Locations; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Lanterns/Lamps; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (front right) and H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (front left) leading members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right of second row)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 23.8 x 29 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Street Lamps; Buildings; Swimming Pools; Men; Group Portraits; Pakistan; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Crowds; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - From the left: H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials
  - From the right, front row: H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr greeting members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Pakistan; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Ceremonies; Gatherings
  - From the left: a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, a member of the Pakistani delegation, Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba speaking to two unidentified men near an airplane., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Airplanes; Transportation; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Hats; Officials; Ceremonies; Gatherings
  - From the right, front row: an unidentified man, H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba, Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr greeting members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 30.4 x 25.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Flags; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Carpets/Rugs; Officials; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) greeting Yahya Khan (left), Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Officials; Pakistan; Gatherings; Clocks/Watches; Furnishings
  - Members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegations having a meal, including H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (left, sitting) and starting third from the right: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Carpets/Rugs; Street Lamps; Buildings; Mountains/Hills; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Regional/National Dress; Presidents; Royalty; Pakistan; Microphones; Hats; Umbrellas/Parasols; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Marching Band; Uniforms; Gatherings
  - From the left: a member of the Pakistani delegation, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, a member of the Pakistani delegation, Ahmad Bin Khalifa Al Yousef, H.E. Abdul Jalil Al Fahim, and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba speaking to two unidentified men near an airplane., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000018_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Gatherings; Ceremonies
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations gathered for a meal, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (foreground, in Emirati dress)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000019_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Waiting staff/Servers; Uniforms; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Paintings; Officials; Pakistan
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with two members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000020_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cigarettes; Smoking; Hats; Clocks/Watches; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages
  - Yahya Khan delivering a speech, with H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi on the left and H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba on the right., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000021_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Waiting staff/Servers; Uniforms; Microphones; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Officials; Presidents; Drinks/Beverages; Food; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Paintings
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan viewing the unveiling of a plaque in his honor, including members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegations and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr smoking., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000022_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Ceremonies
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations gathered for a meal, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (foreground, in Emirati dress)., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref19_000023_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Carpets/Rugs; Furnishings; Officials; Paintings; Food; Drinks/Beverages; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Gatherings
- Members of the UAE Delegation Abroad and in the UAE
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan greeting an unidentified man, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left), H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (middle left), and H.E. Sheikh Mubarak Al Nahyan (middle right) at Sheikh Zayed's Diwan., Circa 1969; AD_MC_093_ref20_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 9 x 13.8 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Offices; Gatherings; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Officials; United Arab Emirates
  - A group of three unidentified men sitting in ornate chairs in Sheikh Hamdan Bin Mohammed Al Nahyan's office., Circa 1974-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.8 x 17.7 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Furnishings; United Arab Emirates; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Clocks/Watches
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour, with H.E. Butti Bin Bishr in the background (wearing ghutra)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 13.8 x 18.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Crowds; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Factories; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Workers; Machines; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Unknown Locations
  - The UAE delegation arriving to a country, including H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi (second from the right), H.E. Ahmed Al Hamed (front wearing sunglasses), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.2 x 19.3 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Unknown Locations; Airports; Airplanes; Transportation; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Hats
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour overseas, with H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi (in military uniform), H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (fourth from the right), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the right) in the background (likely to be in Pakistan)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.7 x 19.4 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Factories; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Gatherings; Officials; Machines; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Hats; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) with a group of men who worked under H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan at a delegation meeting in Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref20_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Facial Hair; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Tents; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) with a group of men who worked under H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan at a delegation meeting in Pakistan., Circa 1968; AD_MC_093_ref20_000007_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Officials; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Ceremonies; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Pakistan
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) talking with a member of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000008_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) talking with members of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000009_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Unknown Locations; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Cigarettes; Smoking; Gatherings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) talking with members of a foreign delegation., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000010_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Regional/National Dress; Cigarettes; Smoking; Officials; Unknown Locations
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with an unidentified man., Circa 1968-1971; AD_MC_093_ref20_000011_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Unknown Locations; Officials; Drinks/Beverages; Furnishings
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000012_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 24 x 18.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Women; Jewelry; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Bags/Purses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with a member of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000013_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Pakistan; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Drinks/Beverages; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Members of the Emirati and Pakistani delegations at a gathering for the UAE's arrival to Pakistan, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle, sitting)., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000014_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Gatherings; Carpets/Rugs; Officials; Pakistan; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Hats; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Furnishings; Food; Drinks/Beverages
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (right) talking with three members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000015_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Officials; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gatherings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Drinks/Beverages
  - Members of the Pakistani and Emirati delegations at a gathering, including H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from right) and H.E. Ahmed Bin Sulayem (right)., Circa 1970-1975; AD_MC_093_ref20_000016_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 18.2 x 24 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Head Covers/Veils; Pakistan; Bags/Purses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Officials; Gatherings; Drinks/Beverages
  - H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan on a factory tour overseas, with H.E. Khalfan Al Romaithi (in military uniform), H.E. Khalaf Al Otaiba (left, behind Sheikh Zayed), and H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (third from the right) in the background (likely to be in Pakistan)., Circa 1968-1970; AD_MC_093_ref20_000017_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 25.3 x 30.6 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Unknown Locations; Factories; Military/Soldiers; Hats; Medals/Insignia; Uniforms; Gatherings; Crowds; Machines; Sheikhs; Officials; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
- Members of the UAE Delegation Abroad and in the UAE
  - From the left, in front: H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan, and Ma'ouf Mohammed Al Amri during a visit to Pakistan., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000001_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 11.8 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Officials; Presidents; Royalty; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Chandeliers; Gatherings; Guns; Weapons; Medals/Insignia
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (right) having tea with a member of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000002_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.4 x 14.9 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Tea/Coffee; Drinks/Beverages; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Tents; Carpets/Rugs; Officials; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty; Pakistan
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (second from the left) and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan (middle) reviewing documents with members of the Pakistani delegation., Circa 1970s; AD_MC_093_ref21_000003_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 11.8 x 16.5 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Pakistan; Officials; Chandeliers; Hats; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Medals/Insignia; Sheikhs; Sheikh Zayed bin Sultan Al Nahyan; Presidents; Royalty
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (front) exiting an airplane into a crowd., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000004_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Airplanes; Transportation; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Crowds; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - H.E. Butti Bin Bishr (left) and members of the Emirati delegation arriving to a country overseas., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000005_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 12.6 x 17.2 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Airplanes; Airports; Transportation; Officials; Unknown Locations; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
  - From the left, with faces visible: H.E. Ahmed Al Suwaidi, H.E. Butti Bin Bishr, and H.H. Sheikh Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan speaking to members of a delegation., Circa 1970-1971; AD_MC_093_ref21_000006_000001; 1 Photographic Prints 14.3 x 19.1 cm (E-records AD_MC_093)